Seven-day Yanghang.
.
We will do it later. In this issue, we introduce the electromagnetic penalty in
the park. First of all, we got an electromagnetic penalty. Take a look at it.
There are three of them here.
There are two holes here. There is a soil here. Take a look at the ab tape.
Below is the rps tape to take a look. In fact, this circuit.
This circuit is what passes through the action of this coil, which is normally
open and turns into a wall. You don’t think that’s enough, right? Dai Haihai,
this is a.
Ab Let’s take a look at the rps below. A friend said how to wire this TV. The
wiring is very simple.
It&#39;s very simple. The last year&#39;s one is the recommended method we
introduced. It&#39;s separate. Take a look at it when you pull it down. It&#39;s
probably going to be miserable when you come over. There&#39;s a monitor here.
There are two access poles here. You have connected them to the movie. There is
a voltage ac-212vac-212v on it. What does ac mean alternating current 212v? I
don&#39;t think it is nuclear.
Nr and sub-pairs do not correspond. This is 60. Blunt, although the electrons in
the tree are not much different.
.
I looked at aclr من there.
The other coordination is simple. After you connect it now, when you grab him,
let him grab the girl and the silk bag. However, the principle of TV
transmission is actually very simple. If it costs 10,000,
There are 24-frame lathes this time, but not many 11-frame lathes. This one is
2.2. This time the wiring is very simple. Its unit is Zhao Palin&#39;s one-step.
On this trail, it is a climb. Wait and think about whether it is right. It is
actually very simple. After connecting the pole, you use the pole to blow and
then see which channel.
Then you go to the regular electricity store and make a phone call. It&#39;s
actually very simple. It&#39;s just like this lamp set, just look at
everyone&#39;s understanding of it. Just have a two-bowl electricity supply and
that&#39;s it.
More is enough. Processed.
.
You don’t know me I know you I know you I know you I know you I know you I know
you I know you I know you I know you I know you I know you I know you I know you
I know you I know you I know you You I know you I know you I know you I know you
I know you I know you I know you I know you I know you I know you I know you.